<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STV</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Salah time Vibration</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">To offer salah correctly.</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Exit</string>
    <string name="menu_home">STV</string>
    <string name="vibration_home">Vibration</string>
    <string name="info">Information</string>
    <string name="compass">Compass</string>
    <string name="home">Contact us</string>

    <string name="long_string">
         <br />\n
         <br />\n
        \n
        \n
                                                    \n \nاردو میں:-\n
        \n<br />
        \n<br />یہ ایپ آپ کے دیگر ڈیٹا اور اسناد کو متاثر نہیں کرتی ہے۔
        \n<br />یہ ایپ آپ کے ڈسٹرب نہ موڈ میں ترمیم کو برقرار رکھتی ہے۔
       \n<br /> یہ خودکار وائبریشن/عام ایپ ہے۔
       \n<br /> اس ایپ کا زیادہ سے زیادہ فوکس صلاۃ کے وقت وائبریشن پر ہے۔
       \n<br /> ہم سب جانتے ہیں کہ نماز میں مسئلہ پیدا ہوتا ہے۔
        \n<br />یہ ایپ آپ کے وائبریشن کو خود بخود چلا کر اس مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔
       \n<br /> اس ایپ میں کسی بھی جسم کے جذبات کے متعلقہ اجزاء نہیں ہیں۔
        \n<br />
        <br />
        \n<br />\nIn English:-
        \n<br />
        <br />
        \nThis app does not affect your other data and credentials.<br />
        \nThis app keeps your do not disturb mode modify.<br />
        \nIt is automatic vibration/normal app.<br />
        \nMaximum focus of this app is on the salah time vibration.<br />
        \nWe all of us know the problem generates in the salah.<br />
        \nThis app solves that problem by automatically executing your vibration.<br />
        \nThis app has not relative components of emotion of any body.<br />
        \n<br />
        
        <br />\nIn Hindi:-
        \n<br />
        <br />
        यह ऐप आपके अन्य डेटा और क्रेडेंशियल को प्रभावित नहीं करता है।<br />\n
        यह ऐप आपके परेशान न करें मोड को संशोधित रखता है।<br />\n
        यह स्वचालित कंपन/सामान्य ऐप है।<br />\n
        इस ऐप का अधिकतम फोकस नमाज के समय कंपन पर है।<br />\n
        हम सभी जानते हैं कि नमाज़ में समस्या उत्पन्न होती है।<br />\n
        यह ऐप आपके कंपन को स्वचालित रूप से निष्पादित करके उस समस्या को हल करता है।<br />\n
        इस ऐप में किसी भी शरीर की भावना के सापेक्ष घटक नहीं हैं।<br />\n

</string>
    <string name="long_string2">
        <br />
        <br />\n
        <br />\nIn English:-
        <br />\n
        <br />
        \nFor using this app do not disturb mode is necessary to allow to switch on and off the vibration/normal mode of your phone.<br />
        \nIn vibration there is all the times are set for salah within a day.<br />
        \nIf user will allow it.<br />
        \nThe vibration mode will by it self on at the salah time and after the salah it will by it self on the normal mode.<br />
        \nThis is automatic app.<br />
        \nOnce you allow the salah times then it will by it self execute daily.<br />
        \nIf you want any time to not change your phone mode switch off the salah time.<br />
        \nAs we know everywhere the salah time is different in each mosque so this app will on your vibration mode for at least<br />
        \nThe problem for which this app is developed as a solution is Salah phone ringing problem.<br />
        \nIf there is any issue you are facing contact with and send us the problem you are facing.<br />
        \n<br />
        \n<br />
         <br />
         <br />
                                                     \nاردو میں:-\n
        <br />\n
        <br />

        اس ایپ کو استعمال کرنے کے لیے آپ کے فون کے وائبریشن/نارمل موڈ کو آن اور آف کرنے کی اجازت دینے کے لیے ڈسٹرب نہ موڈ ضروری ہے۔<br />\n
        وائبریشن میں ایک دن میں صلاۃ کے تمام اوقات مقرر ہیں۔<br />\n
        اگر صارف اس کی اجازت دے گا۔<br />\n
        وائبریشن موڈ خود نماز کے وقت اور نماز کے بعد خود بخود نارمل موڈ پر ہوگا۔<br />\n
        یہ خودکار ایپ ہے۔<br />\n
        ایک بار جب آپ صلاۃ کے اوقات کی اجازت دے دیں گے تو اس کے ذریعہ روزانہ خود عمل ہو گا۔<br />\n
        اگر آپ کسی بھی وقت اپنے فون کا موڈ تبدیل نہ کرنا چاہتے ہیں تو صلاۃ کا وقت بند کر دیں۔<br />\n
        جیسا کہ ہم جانتے ہیں کہ ہر جگہ ہر مسجد میں نماز کا وقت مختلف ہوتا ہے لہذا یہ ایپ آپ کے وائبریشن موڈ پر کم از کم<br />\n
        اس ایپ کو جس مسئلے کے حل کے طور پر تیار کیا گیا ہے وہ صلاح فون کی گھنٹی کا مسئلہ ہے۔<br />\n
        اگر آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہے تو رابطہ کریں اور ہمیں جو مسئلہ درپیش ہے اسے بھیجیں۔<br />\n

        <br />\n\n
        <br />In Hindi:-<br />
        <br />\n
        इस ऐप का उपयोग करने के लिए डू नॉट डिस्टर्ब मोड आवश्यक है ताकि आपके फोन के कंपन/सामान्य मोड को चालू और बंद किया जा सके।<br />
        \nकंपन में हर समय एक दिन के भीतर सलाहा के लिए निर्धारित किया जाता है।<br />
        \nयदि उपयोगकर्ता इसकी अनुमति देगा।<br />
        \nसलाह के समय कंपन मोड अपने आप चालू हो जाएगा और सलाह के बाद यह अपने आप सामान्य मोड पर हो जाएगा।<br />
        \nयह स्वचालित ऐप है।<br />
        \nएक बार जब आप नमाज़ के समय की अनुमति देते हैं तो यह दैनिक रूप से स्वयं निष्पादित हो जाएगा।<br />
        \nयदि आप चाहते हैं कि किसी भी समय आपका फ़ोन मोड न बदले तो सलाहा समय बंद कर दें।<br />
        \nजैसा कि हम हर जगह जानते हैं कि हर मस्जिद में सलाहा का समय अलग होता है, इसलिए यह ऐप आपके कंपन मोड पर कम से कम<br />
        \nजिस समस्या के समाधान के रूप में इस ऐप को विकसित किया गया है वह है सालाह फोन बजने की समस्या।<br />
        \nयदि कोई समस्या है जिसके साथ आप संपर्क कर रहे हैं और हमें वह समस्या भेजें जिसका आप सामना कर रहे हैं।<br />
        \n<br />
        \n<br />
    </string>
    <string name="accept_switch">Allow it</string>
    <string name="term_string">Terms and execution</string>
    <string name="long_string3">\n\n\nFaizul haque built the Salah time vibration app as a Free app.\nThis SERVICE is provided by faizul haque at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.\n

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.\n The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service.\n I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at my app unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n
\n
 \n
Information Collection and Use
\n
For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to allow the do not disturb mode .\nThe information that I request will not be harming you device.\n


I may require your allowance for following reasons :\n

To facilitate our Service;\n
To provide the Service on our behalf;\n
To perform Service-related services;\n
To provide you knowledge and help.\n
I want to inform users of this Service that this app will provide is very important for you at salah time.\n The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf.\n

I value your trust in providing us , thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.\n
\n
Changes to This Privacy Policy\n

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time.\n Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes.\n I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.\n
\n
Contact Us
\n
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at faizhaque35@gmail.com.

This privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and modified/generated by App Privacy Policy Generator</string>
</resources>